Anyone else would be dead by now.
The Losers is a action, adventure, crime film directed by Sylvain White.
On a mission deep in the Bolivian jungle, a team of elite commandos
finds itself on the receiving end of a lethal betrayal.
Now presumed dead, the men join forces with a mysterious operative
named Aisha to hunt down their enemy and even the score.
Clay, played by Jeffrey Dean Morgan.
Aisha, played by Zoe Saldaña.
Jensen, played by Chris Evans.
Roque, played by Idris Elba.
Pooch, played by Columbus Short.
Cougar, played by Óscar Jaenada.
The Losers is a 2010 American action comedy film directed by Sylvain White and written by Peter
Berg and James Vanderbilt, based on the comic book series by Andy Diggle and Jock.
The film features an ensemble cast starring Jeffrey Dean Morgan, Chris Evans, Zoe
Saldaña, Idris Elba, Columbus Short, Óscar Jaenada and Jason Patric.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and drew comparisons to The A-Team, a
remake of which was released shortly after The Losers premiered.
The film explores themes of based on comic, hospital, black ops.
The tone is intense and thought_provoking and mind_bending.